<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<contentlist>
	<!-- This file contains the getting started documentation from wpdojoloader -->
	
	<content id="###right###" group="gettingstarted">
		<div style="padding:10px;">
		<span mark="install">
			<b>Installation</b><br/>
			<br/>
			The installion is just easy. Extract the wpdojoloader.zip under the wordpress/wp-content/plugins directory so that you have a subfolder which is called wpdojoloader.<br/>
			(A small hint: wpdojoloader does not require to overwrite any other wordpress files,
			exempt from a previous wpdojoloader installation.<br/>So if you're beeing asked... There's probably something wrong ! )<br/>
			<br/><br/>			
		</span>	 
		
		<span mark="configuration">
			<b>Configuration</b><br/>
			<br/>
			With a normal wordpress configuration you should not have to configure anything.
			But if you are using a wordpress multi installation you probably have to configure
			the path to the wordpress content directory if you are using a datagrid.
			In the wpdojoloader.php you find a section called "Beging Config Section" there you can
			change some settings.
		</span>
		
		<span mark="activate">
			<b>Activate the plugin</b><br/>
			<br/>
			Just go to settings -> wpdojoloader<br/>
			Check if "Activate Dojo Loader Plugin?" is "yes" scroll down and click update settings...
			<br/><br/>
			That's it: <br/>
			<img src="doc/img/activate.jpg" />			
		</span>
		<span mark="hello">
			<b>Hello World</b><br/>
			<br/>		
			In this chapter i describe how wpdojoloader works generally so that you get an idea of
			what you can do.<br/>
			<br/> 
			So, first of all we create a new post:<br/>
			<img src="doc/img/add_post.jpg" />	
			<br/>
			<b>Next</b> we have to say that we are creating dojoloader content.
			This is done with the dojocontent start and end tag.<br/>
			If dojoloader is active you have a new button in your editor. With that button
			you can easy insert dojoloader text.<br/><br/>
			Click the Button select dojo content tags:<br/>
			<img src="doc/img/add_content_tags_1.jpg" /><br/><br/>
			<b>And</b> then you should have something like this:<br/>
			<img src="doc/img/add_content_tags_2.jpg" /><br/><br/><br/>
			<b>Now</b> we want to have a accordion. Just click the dojoloader button again, select
			accordion and that's it.<br/>
			<b>Step 1</b>
			<img src="doc/img/add_accordion_1.jpg" /><br/><br/><br/>
			<b>Step 2</b>
			<img src="doc/img/add_accordion_2.jpg" /><br/>
			<br/><br/>
			<b>Now</b> you can save the post (or page) and click the "View Post" button.
			The result is something like this:<br/>				
			<img src="doc/img/view_accordion_1.jpg" /><br/>
			<br/><br/>
			<b>At</b> the moment you don't have your own text in the accordion. You just see the
			content placeholders (the text with the hash keys).<br/>
			In the editor menu you can also select a content element.<br/>
			Select it, change the id attribute to for the content which you want to enter, change the title
			(the title attribute is not used by all widgets) and then add some text:<br/>
			<img src="doc/img/add_accordion_3.jpg" /><br/>
			<br/><br/>
			<b>Save</b> the post again and now it looks like this:
			<br/>
			<img src="doc/img/view_accordion_2.jpg" /><br/>
			<br/><br/><br/>
			<h1><b>ready !</b></h1>						
		</span>
		</div>
	</content>

</contentlist>